{
  "page113" : {
    "question01" : {
      "question" : "hekí",
      "answer" : "see"
    },
    "question02" : {
      "question" : "hekíce",
      "answer" : "see (1st, 2nd person)"
    },
    "question03" : {
      "question" : "'iin hekíce",
      "answer" : "I see"
    },
    "question04" : {
      "question" : "'iim hekíce",
      "answer" : "you see"
    },
    "question05" : {
      "question" : "heekíce",
      "answer" : "see (3rd person)"
    },
    "question06" : {
      "question" : "'ipí heekíce",
      "answer" : "he/she/it sees"
    },
    "question07" : {
      "question" : "hekcíix",
      "answer" : "see (plural)"
    },
    "question08" : {
      "question" : "nuun hekcíix",
      "answer" : "we (exclusive) see"
    },
    "question09" : {
      "question" : "kiye hekcíix",
      "answer" : "we (inclusive) see"
    },
    "question10" : {
      "question" : "'eetx hekcíix",
      "answer" : "you (plural) see"
    },
    "question11" : {
      "question" : "heekcíix",
      "answer" : "see (3rd person plural)"
    },
    "question12" : {
      "question" : "'imé heekcíix",
      "answer" : "they (plural) sees"
    },
    "question13" : {
      "question" : "wéewluq",
      "answer" : "want"
    },
    "question14" : {
      "question" : "wéewluqse",
      "answer" : "want (1st, 2nd person)"
    },
    "question15" : {
      "question" : "'iin wéewluqse",
      "answer" : "I want"
    },
    "question16" : {
      "question" : "'iim wéewluqse",
      "answer" : "you want"
    },
    "question17" : {
      "question" : "hiwéewluqse",
      "answer" : "want (3rd person)"
    },
    "question18" : {
      "question" : "'ipí hiwéewluqse",
      "answer" : "he/she/it wants"
    },
    "question19" : {
      "question" : "wéewluqsix",
      "answer" : "want (plural)"
    },
    "question20" : {
      "question" : "nuun wéewluqsix",
      "answer" : "we (exclusive) want"
    },
    "question21" : {
      "question" : "kiye wéewluqsix",
      "answer" : "we (inclusive) want"
    },
    "question22" : {
      "question" : "'eetx wéewluqsix",
      "answer" : "you (plural) want"
    },
    "question23" : {
      "question" : "hiwéewlusqix",
      "answer" : "want (3rd person plural)"
    },
    "question24" : {
      "question" : "'imé hiwéewluqsix",
      "answer" : "they (plural) want"
    },
    "question25" : {
      "question" : "k'óomay",
      "answer" : "hurt, sick"
    },
    "question26" : {
      "question" : "k'óomayca",
      "answer" : "hurt, sick (1st, 2nd person)"
    },
    "question27" : {
      "question" : "hik'óomyca",
      "answer" : "hurt, sick (3rd person)"
    },
    "question28" : {
      "question" : "k'óomaycix",
      "answer" : "hurt, sick (plural)"
    },
    "question29" : {
      "question" : "hik'óomaycix",
      "answer" : "hurt, sick (3rd person plural)"
    },
    "question30" : {
      "question" : "'iin k'óomyca",
      "answer" : "I am hurt or sick"
    },
    "question31" : {
      "question" : "'iim k'óomayca",
      "answer" : "you are hurt or sick"
    },
    "question32" : {
      "question" : "'ipí hik'óomayca",
      "answer" : "he/she/it is hurt or sick"
    },
    "question33" : {
      "question" : "nuun k'óomaycix",
      "answer" : "we (exclusive) are hurt or sick"
    },
    "question34" : {
      "question" : "kiye k'óomaycix",
      "answer" : "we (inclusive) are hurt or sick"
    },
    "question35" : {
      "question" : "'eetx k'óomaycix",
      "answer" : "you (group) are sick"
    },
    "question36" : {
      "question" : "'imé hik'óomaycix"
    },
    "question37" : {
      "question" : "kuu",
      "answer" : "go, do"
    },
    "question38" : {
      "question" : "kúuse",
      "answer" : "go, do (1st, 2nd person)"
    },
    "question39" : {
      "question" : "hikúuse",
      "answer" : "go, do (3rd person)"
    },
    "question40" : {
      "question" : "kusíix",
      "answer" : "go, do (plural)"
    },
    "question41" : {
      "question" : "hikusíix",
      "answer" : "go, do (3rd person plural)"
    },
    "question42" : {
      "question" : "'iin kúuse",
      "answer" : "I go or do"
    },
    "question43" : {
      "question" : "'iim kúuse",
      "answer" : "you go or do"
    },
    "question44" : {
      "question" : "'ipí hikúuse",
      "answer" : "he/she/it goes or does"
    },
    "question45" : {
      "question" : "nuun kusíix",
      "answer" : "we (exclusive) go or do"
    },
    "question46" : {
      "question" : "kiye kusíix",
      "answer" : "we (inclusive) go or do"
    },
    "question47" : {
      "question" : "'eetx kusíix",
      "answer" : "you (plural) go or do"
    },
    "question48" : {
      "question" : "'imé hikusíix",
      "answer" : "they (plural) go or do"
    }
  },
  "page114" : {
    "question01" : {
      "question" : "'iin wáaqca",
      "answer" : "I wake up"
    },
    "question02" : {
      "question" : "'ee wáaqca",
      "answer" : "you wake up"
    }
  }
}